Emad Ghassan Abd

Human Resource Manager - Administrator

Summary

Human Resource Management With 3+ Years Of Experience Like Training And Staff Support, Preparing And Updating Employment Records Related To Hiring, Transferring, Promoting, And Terminating, Compiling Reports And, Performing Payroll And Benefits Audits And I Have Experienced Administrator With Excellent Management Skills.

Personal Info-

Date of Birth: 01/17/1992

Gender: Male **Nationality:** Iraqi

Email:emadenezy@yahoo.co.uk Phone Number:07700271011 Address: IQ - Baghdad / Al-Mansour

SKILLS

- Excellent MS Office Skills Especially Word, Excel And Outlook.
- Excellent Adobe Photoshop Skills.
- Strong Computer Skills.
- Administrative Experience.
- Human Resources Experience.
- Preparing Spreadsheets.
- Excellent Reporting Skills.

Qualifications

- Communication Skills.
- Flexible Time.
- Problem Solving Skills.
- Multi-Tasking.
- Teamwork.
- Ability to Work Under Pressure.
- Leadership.
- Ability to Travelling.
- Creativity.
- Organizational Skills.
- Responsible.
- Motivational
- Decision Making
- Conflict Resolution
- Negotiations
- Customer Service.

Education

 Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science.

University: Baghdad College of Economic Sciences University

Awards And Certification

- HRM (Human Resorcse Management) Institute: IBMI Berlin – Germany

Date: 1/5/2019

Language

English - Excellent In Speak Good
In Writing

EXPERIENCE

- Supervisor. Steamroller Driver (June 2011 – Dec 2012)

Company: Histyar Group (IQ / Sulaymaniyah)

- Responsibilities Of Road Roller Used For Paving, Surfacing, Applying Concrete, Asphalt.
- Other Materials To Build Up Road And Building.

Assistant Store Manager (Employment Contract) (Sep 2014 – June 2015)

Company: University Of Baghdad / College Of Engineering. (IQ – Baghdad)

- Assists The Store Manager In Motivating And Inspiring Our Team To Achieve Store Productivity Goals.
- Maintain and Monitor Store Inventory.
- Ensure that the store Is Clean And Safe.
- Generate And Review Daily Sales Report.

- HR Assistant (Sep 2015 - Jan 2016)

Company: Al-Taakah Al-Petrolia, Al-Jandar (Oil Product)

- Deal with Employee Requests Regarding Human Resources Issues , Rules , And Regulations
- Welcomes New Employees To The Organization By Conducting Orientation.
- Provides Secretarial Support By Entering, Formatting, And Printing Information Organizing Work.
- Compiling Reports and Spread Sheets and Preparing Spreadsheets.

- HR Assistant, Accountant (Feb 2016 –July 2016)

Company: MADO Restaurant – Mall Al-Mansour (IQ – Baghdad)

- Processing Payroll, Which Includes Ensuring Vacation And Sick Time Are Tracked In The System.
- Maintains The Work Structure By Updating Job Requirements And Job Descriptions For All Positions.
- Preparing And Updating Employment Records Related To Hiring, Transferring, Promoting, And Terminating.
- Updating and Maintaining Employee Benefits, Employment Status, and Similar Records.
- Training and Staff Support.
- Support The Accounting Department By Performing Clerical Tasks, Including Processing And Recording Transactions.

- Branch Manager (July 2016 - Jan 2019)

Company: MADO Restaurant – Mall Al-Mansour (IQ – Baghdad).

- Directing All Operational Aspects Including Distribution, Customer Service, Administration And Sales In Accordance With The Objectives.
- Human Resource Responsibilities.
- Providing Training, Coaching, Development And Motivation For Employees.
- Developing Forecasts, Financial Objectives And Business Plans.
- Manage Budget And Allocate Funds Appropriately.
- Share Knowledge with Other Branches and Headquarters On Effective Practices, Competitive Intelligence, Business Opportunities And Needs.
- Compiling Reports and Spread Sheets And Preparing Spreadsheets.
- Developing Forecasts, Financial Objectives And Business Plans .